NOOR UL AIN BABWANI

C6 Lakhani Towers Nishter Road Garden West, Karachi Sindh Email: babwani.noorulain@gmail.com Contact: +92-333-3081031

Objective

To acquire dynamic experience and knowledge in the field of pharmacy, where I can apply my skills and knowledge in the areas of dispensing correct medication, pharmacy communications and knowledge of prescription drugs, and to create drugs for the diseases which are presently incurable and mostly enhance my skills and learning in a professional environment by which I can aid the people for the advancement of their health in life.

Field of Interests

Quality Assurance, Dispensing Medications, Drugs Packaging, Quality Control, Drugs Designing and Management of medicines.

Work Experiences

Aga Khan Welfare Board For Garden Ibn-e-Sina Pharmacy

April 2015 - Present

- Dispensing Medicines to out-patients.
- Data Entry of Medications in Pharmaceutical system.
- Stock checking and Inventory of drugs.

Sanofi-Aventis Pakistan

IQC Department

December 2014 - January 2015

- Under the supervision of Sanofi Pharmacists, I have learned the basic operational skills.
- Issuing of line clearance at every step of batch manufacturing.
- Maintaining and updating the Batch Manufacturing Records.
- Documentation of log books, calibration records and temperature records.
- Assisted in production and performing in-process quality assurance checks of tablets and capsules.
- Have worked actively in Quality Assurance Department with learning in tablet data entering.

Aga Khan Maternal and Child Care Center, Hyderabad Pharmacy Department

April 2014 - July 2014

- Dispensing Medicines to In/Out Patients
- Prescription Handling
- Dispensing of Take-home Medications
- Medication and Vaccination Inventoy
- Checking of Stock Medications

Education

2009 - 2013

Bachelors in Pharm-D

Sindh University Jamshoro, Hyderabad

2008

Intermediate (H.S.C)

County Girls College, Hyderabad

2006

Matriculation (S.S.C)

St. Bonaventure's High School Qasimabad, Hyderabad

Technical Skills

- Familiar with Microsoft Word and Microsoft PowerPoint.
- Proficient in Writing and Communicating Urdu and English.
- Manage time effectively and Completion of Tasks within due date
- Team Work and ability to withstand in Critical Situations
- Emailing and Printing
- Internet Surfing

Certifications

Mental Health First Aid Pakistan Course	l Mashal, Aman Foundation Karachi
Mental Health First Ald Pakistan Course	į įviasnai,

August 2014

Enrich Your Skills | Aga Khan Economic Planning Board

2011

Academic & Leadership Training | Aga Khan Education Board, Hyderabad

Women Leaders of Tomorrow

2008

Service bar Pakistan Girls Guide Association

Outdoor Activity & Physical Health

2008

Girls Guide Camp Pakistan Girls Guide Association

2006

Training Completion | Focus Humanitarian Assistance Pakistan

First Aid, Fire Fighting, Search & Rescue for disaster

Voluntary Services

Aga Khan Social Welfare Board December 2014 – Present

Incharge, Mental Health

Aminabad Girls Guide Association Hyderabad | 2002 – 2010

Member

Aminabad Religious Education Center | 2006 – 2008

Primary Teacher

Personal Information

Father Name: Amjad Ali Nationality: Pakistani